<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>life - Tag - Gavin Mead</title>
        <link>https://gavinmead.sh/tags/life/</link>
        <description>life - Tag - Gavin Mead</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:22:23 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gavinmead.sh/tags/life/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>An occasional miss</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-21/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:22:23 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-21/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Traded slow productivity for a few days of extreme productivity. Nothing is for free and the cost was time for other things. Missed some daily C++, exercise and site updates. This is fine as an occassional miss, but not to become routine. A bit of reflection and resetting is necessary. It happens sometimes&hellip;]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Marathons</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-18/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:50:44 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-18/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sometimes deep work can be a ton of fun. Especially when you reach a flow state. I don&rsquo;t celebrate this, but I was having a hard time sleeping so decided to wake up to do some work (for the job, not C++). I found myself being incredibly productive and thus completely lost track of time. All told, I looked up at and it was 4am. I wasn&rsquo;t tired, in fact, I was quite energized.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Big Bets</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-17/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:52:41 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-17/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[&lsquo;Big&rsquo; is all relative here. But sometimes there is a need to take a big swing and do something that feels immensely uncomfortable. It can mean going against the status quo or going out on your own. I have a lot of respect for the folks who step into the arena and take a shot. It is something that I admire and I have to work myself up towards doing more often.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>June 16-22 Week in Review</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-09-week-in-review/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 10:23:45 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-09-week-in-review/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This was an uneventful week. A lot of professional work intruded on slow productivity, but will get back to normal soon.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Chances</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-15/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 14:19:42 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-15/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I don&rsquo;t use social media other than LinkedIn and rarely do I share anything. I&rsquo;ll like things that others share, but I am generally quite reticient. I don&rsquo;t know where that comes from other than a fear of something. Probably criticism. But that is something that I am working on. I wanted to share an experience I had after going for a walk at my alma-mater George Mason University. I spent too much time on it, but it was also a good writing exercise and I&rsquo;m glad I did it.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Under the wire</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-14/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 22:54:16 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-14/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A bit of a crazy day, but still trying to maintain the habit of a daily post.
I visited my old my university today. I&rsquo;ll probably write more about that another day. I just took a walk while my son had soccer practice. I thought about good (and bad) memories, but really how the course of my life changed though chance encounters and making connections with people during my time there.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Syncopation</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-13/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2024 21:56:31 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-13/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sometimes a break in an expectation can lead to great results. It helps you challenge assumptions about what comes next and keeps you engaged. Rhythm is important, but every now and then it is fun to change things up.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Create a new homeostasis</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-12/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:24:10 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-12/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[When I try to grow there is an inevitable pull towards a previous homestasis that is difficult to push through sometimes. I&rsquo;m catching myself now. I have a decent amount of professional work to do that I am excited for, but I can already feel it creeping into my other interests of slow productivity. This is to be fought since the work will always be there. Spending an hour on important things does not make or break anything with the work that will be waiting for you.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Gratitude</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-11/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 19:36:21 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-11/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Gratitude is a nice way to start or end any day. It is useful at the end; especially if the day was less than ideal because it will shift you towards something positive. It is a common practice as a prompt for daily journaling. I have a section for gratitude in my morning pages template, but, I don&rsquo;t always follow it. It says &ldquo;I am grateful for&rdquo; and then I list some things.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Tradeoffs</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-10/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 17:52:58 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-10/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Focus on the things that matter to you and find opportunities to cut out noise. As I&rsquo;ve gotten older the only thing that really matters to me is my time. But, I am not always so great at utilizing my time as wisely as I could. This happens because it is difficult to say no or my curiousity gets the better of me instead of staying focused on a few things.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
