<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Gavin Mead</title>
        <link>https://gavinmead.sh/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Gavin Mead</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:25:27 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gavinmead.sh/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Connection</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-06/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 21:25:27 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-06/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;ve become pretty introverted as I&rsquo;ve gotten older. But, every now and then I&rsquo;m reminded of why connecting with people is so important. You find that you aren&rsquo;t alone in your insecurities, that we have shared experiences of self-doubt or imposter syndrome that never goes away. It is a relief.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Being of service</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-05/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 21:22:13 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-05/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Guiding and helping other people is pretty great and something that I&rsquo;ve grown into over the last few years. I never thought of myself as a leader and was quite reluctant to embrace that as a thing that mattered. But, I have found that helping others, especially teaching has been incredibly rewarding and I am always so happy when I see people grow.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Hold high standards for yourself</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-04/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 19:16:27 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-04/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Systems are important to drive identity changes; James Clear taught me that. In particular, I did not sleep well last night. I slept in so I was not as tired. When that happens I tend to get restless. I made the conscious choice to force myself awake at 5am (my goal wake up time) no matter what time I fell asleep (it was around 1am). It would have two benefits. First, I&rsquo;d get back to my morning routine, and two, I&rsquo;m pretty tired right now, so confidence is high that I&rsquo;ll sleep better.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Use the tools you have</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-03/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2024 18:49:16 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-03/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I sometimes catch myself thinking if I just had X then Y would happen. I tried this when I picked up the guitar again during the pandemic. The equipment and amp sims that I purchased were more than enough for what I wanted to do, but it didn&rsquo;t sound quite the way I wanted. I was spoiled by the good audio mixes you hear on guitar youtube and I figured I could buy my way out of not practicing.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>May 26-June 1 Week in Review</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-26-week-in-review/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 10:05:48 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-26-week-in-review/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A delightful week of slow productivity. A few fun things to share.
Podcasts I enjoyed The Tim Ferriss Show two for one with Brene Brown and Edward O. Thorp. The Rich Roll Podcast with Dan Churchill. Technically, I listened to this last week, but wanted to share. Resources I&rsquo;ve been using for C++ and
Things that have me curious Rucking as a means of improving my health. I am not a runner and while I like walking, I&rsquo;d like to get more out of it.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bias Towards Action</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-01/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:01:28 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-01/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sometimes the best course of action is to just move. Not a particularly deep thought, but for those of us that can get caught up in our own heads, it is a good reminder.
It is easy to fall into the doom loop of questioning everything; imagining every possible outcome. &ldquo;What about this&hellip;what about that&rdquo;? This is probably not the best use of time. Focusing on the important questions is a matter of high judgement with some intuition about the questions weight.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Do Hard Things</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-31/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-31/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[For me personally, waking up at 5am is not too difficult. Heavy deadlifts at 5:45am in the morning is not as easy. The excuses and justifcations for why you cannot or should not do it start to creep in, but in reality like many things, we suffer more in imagination than reality.
Always do the first set; especially when you don&rsquo;t want to. That&rsquo;s the point.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bubbling Up</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-30/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 17:27:10 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-30/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The things you care about really do bubble to the top of your todo list.
Right now I am prioritizing slow productivity in my personal life; focusing on consistent exercise, learning C++ and updating this site. I notice that other things that I thought I cared about have fallen away.
At work, it is building a customer experience for a platform I support. I find that I truly care about making something that works for people, it is energizing.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Magical Truth Seeking</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-29/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:01:57 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-29/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Magic really does happen in the truth seeking of differing points of view. It can be really awesome when you open yourself up to feedback and are not super attached to your own ideas.
Updates:
Added ideas in gm-git regarding command link flag handling. ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Slow Productivity</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-28/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:27:50 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-28/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I am on a general search for balance and consistency. I was listening a few months ago to an episode of The Tim Ferriss Show that talked about slow productivity. I am going to give it another listen, but something that stuck with me was the consistency of practice. I heard it but it didn&rsquo;t click. Then I heard a similar thing in an interview with Seth Godin where he commits to writing everyday.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
