<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Gavin Mead</title>
        <link>https://gavinmead.sh/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 22:16:48 -0400</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://gavinmead.sh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Positive Intent</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-19/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jul 2024 22:16:48 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-19/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Always assume people mean well. It is a great feeling.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Don&#39;t wait until you are ready</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-18/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 20:09:22 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-18/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m reading &lsquo;Hidden Potential&rsquo; by Adam Grant and one of the areas around growth is that you have be willing to fail alot and to start before you think you are ready. Just keep trying. If you fail, reflect and adjust and try again.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Why Worry</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-17/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 00:12:26 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-17/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sometimes getting stuck in your own head is inevitable and the suffering of imagination starts to feel real. Remember that if you can solve it (or at least get out of your head) then why worry. If you can&rsquo;t get out of your head right now, you will eventually, so why worry.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Recharge</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-16/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 18:19:48 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-07-16/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[It is great to get away from the regular routine. It is especially great when you can unplug and see someplace new. The ocean is meditative and being next to it, but in a new part of the world was wonderful. I don&rsquo;t have a ton of my mind today, but will get back to a few more words starting tomorrow.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>A Drive into the Paint</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-25/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 18:31:17 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-25/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to drive hard and get knocked around. You could take serious contact and not get help, but sometimes it is necessary. It is sometimes necessary to disrupt and shake things up. It isn&rsquo;t comfortable or fun and can get you into trouble, but sometimes it is worth it. Even though this is a basketball analogy, perhaps a hockey fight is more apt. Players may decide to fight to help amp up their team.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>June 16-22 Week in Review</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-16-week-in-review/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 09:08:26 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-16-week-in-review/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>An occasional miss</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-21/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 05:22:23 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-21/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Traded slow productivity for a few days of extreme productivity. Nothing is for free and the cost was time for other things. Missed some daily C++, exercise and site updates. This is fine as an occassional miss, but not to become routine. A bit of reflection and resetting is necessary. It happens sometimes&hellip;]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Marathons</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-18/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2024 19:50:44 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-18/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sometimes deep work can be a ton of fun. Especially when you reach a flow state. I don&rsquo;t celebrate this, but I was having a hard time sleeping so decided to wake up to do some work (for the job, not C++). I found myself being incredibly productive and thus completely lost track of time. All told, I looked up at and it was 4am. I wasn&rsquo;t tired, in fact, I was quite energized.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Big Bets</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-17/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 17:52:41 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-17/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[&lsquo;Big&rsquo; is all relative here. But sometimes there is a need to take a big swing and do something that feels immensely uncomfortable. It can mean going against the status quo or going out on your own. I have a lot of respect for the folks who step into the arena and take a shot. It is something that I admire and I have to work myself up towards doing more often.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>June 16-22 Week in Review</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-09-week-in-review/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2024 10:23:45 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-09-week-in-review/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[This was an uneventful week. A lot of professional work intruded on slow productivity, but will get back to normal soon.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
