<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Gavin Mead</title>
        <link>https://gavinmead.sh/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:01:28 -0400</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://gavinmead.sh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Bias Towards Action</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-01/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 07:01:28 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-06-01/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Sometimes the best course of action is to just move. Not a particularly deep thought, but for those of us that can get caught up in our own heads, it is a good reminder.
It is easy to fall into the doom loop of questioning everything; imagining every possible outcome. &ldquo;What about this&hellip;what about that&rdquo;? This is probably not the best use of time. Focusing on the important questions is a matter of high judgement with some intuition about the questions weight.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Do Hard Things</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-31/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 20:24:03 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-31/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[For me personally, waking up at 5am is not too difficult. Heavy deadlifts at 5:45am in the morning is not as easy. The excuses and justifcations for why you cannot or should not do it start to creep in, but in reality like many things, we suffer more in imagination than reality.
Always do the first set; especially when you don&rsquo;t want to. That&rsquo;s the point.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Bubbling Up</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-30/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 17:27:10 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-30/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[The things you care about really do bubble to the top of your todo list.
Right now I am prioritizing slow productivity in my personal life; focusing on consistent exercise, learning C++ and updating this site. I notice that other things that I thought I cared about have fallen away.
At work, it is building a customer experience for a platform I support. I find that I truly care about making something that works for people, it is energizing.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Magical Truth Seeking</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-29/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 21:01:57 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-29/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Magic really does happen in the truth seeking of differing points of view. It can be really awesome when you open yourself up to feedback and are not super attached to your own ideas.
Updates:
Added ideas in gm-git regarding command link flag handling. ]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Slow Productivity</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-28/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:27:50 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/24-05-28/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I am on a general search for balance and consistency. I was listening a few months ago to an episode of The Tim Ferriss Show that talked about slow productivity. I am going to give it another listen, but something that stuck with me was the consistency of practice. I heard it but it didn&rsquo;t click. Then I heard a similar thing in an interview with Seth Godin where he commits to writing everyday.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>gm-git</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/gm-git/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 20:20:29 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/gm-git/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[6/1 Flags Update I&rsquo;m curious if std::variant or std::any could work for the templated approach. I was playing around with a Flag interface and some of the templating seemed weird.
If I want to do that then fixing the bazel build is the next thing. It looks like the cc_toolchain defaults to c++14, and I&rsquo;ll need at least c++17 (23 is ideal) in order to explore that more.
5/29 Slow Productivity: Flags Thinking through some ideas for how to attach flags to the Commands.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>August 6th Week In Review</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/8_6_week_review/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 19:53:58 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/8_6_week_review/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Enjoyed a week of relaxation at the beach. I want to do something similar to the Tim Ferriss 5 Bullet Friday where I share stuff that I found interesting this past week.
Podcasts I enjoyed:
The Tim Ferriss Show episode with Dustin Moskovitz. I&rsquo;m playing around with the time budget google sheet template. The Ethan Hawke episode of Armchair Expert resonated with me. Lots of conversation around taking risks and learning from failure.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Something New</title>
    <link>https://gavinmead.sh/something_new/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 18:36:05 -0400</pubDate>
    <author>Gavin</author>
    <guid>https://gavinmead.sh/something_new/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I have wanted to run a website for a bit to capture fun things that I am up to. I was inspired listening to &ldquo;The Tim Ferriss Show&rdquo; with Derek Sivers episode. In particular, I thought it was super cool the way Sivers achieves tech independence and decided to give it a try.
This site may be nothing or something, but I want to share things I&rsquo;m learning and practice my writing.]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
